but uh
I love whom I stream
it's three tokens for kiss and five
tokens sir nipple flash and whatever
else the girls on my freak am saying
those things definitely if I had
balloons imma pop them but I don't I
play League of Legends bros oh you know
what I was doing tonight though new
Eminem malval is good if you haven't
listened to it yet kamikaze particularly
in the third song I was uh I was
impressed I hated the last one
yeah just lying in bed listening to
Eminem and I was like I'm gonna play
some League Legends and then I was like
but I can't talk to myself when I play
League of Legends and then I was like
that's why I have twitch
all right I'm always misfortune
misfortunes great because she says to
make it rain button 17 people that's
good
brought to you by Lacroix ah delicious
hey let's play all right I'm not gonna
buy guardian angel this time we're only
gonna buy offensive stuff I think well
no maybe boots maybe defense I don't
know there's probably like tutorials on
this online like Google how to be good
at League of Legends
this game also takes forever to load
because Xin Zhao has a crappy computer
good thing he's nothing on their team
yeah guys US isn't cool more we wait I
control my light switch my lights for my
phone look at that
maybe it'll work
okay this usually works oh there we go
look I can tell my lights for my phone
you might think this is meaningless but
my bed is over there and my light
switches over there I used to have to
get up and it was actually one of the
biggest problems in my life now I'm not
really sure what that says about my life
but we can dim a little bit - yeah
that's a lovely ambience nothing's a
waste of time you guys life is
meaningless bullshit I can double click
you know wait what's a waste of time
time is a waste of time but but if my
champion will continue attacking after
only a single click how am I gonna get
my APM up
no-one's going man I'm going men let's
go men
like this guy's going mid there's always
action amid
okay you guys always complain about the
sound I don't believe you
wait is there actually no sound oh shit
no sound sound sound sound sound no
sound stop it
Oh like other guys snipe my goals
okyou is guy
oh my gotta kill that aunty kill that
aunty oh no no no no shit
oh that was just dumb that was just dumb
I'm sorry I suck well at least if at our
kills me nobody actually gets any gold
so it's fine except this is valuable
experience I could be learning earning
earning whatever Annie had to go home
anyway
oh why I'm calling her Annie is her name
Annie
oh yeah knees back
no no no no no no never got another no
run no nun this guy
I'm so bad at this game
can I buy anything yet boo boots okay
this is a real problem they're too good
well you know what maybe I should stay
close to my tower
Oh Annie I'm gonna kill you
but that's my experience I understand
focus on the last hitting of minions
when their health is low okay I
understand I'm gonna I'm gonna hang out
in the bushes and ambush
well how is this guy so good
bullshit
this guy's hack it is he oh okay focus
on last hitting minions okay I
understand you guys give me such good
League of Legends hips
I can't have help how do I gonna kill
him we were close to the same level oh
look at that last hit that was the best
last night I did all game
yeah ya know about our power
whoo
this guy's good now you do have my our
power see this guy's cheated
look at him cheap he's too good
how is he doing that where was she level
18 when I needed help
Oh Annie's back I killed Annie once
no no no no no help me help me help me
oh he ran away whoa whoa what's that
we got anything for killing there okay I
got it make sure to use my affability
don't forget DNA okay so Diaz exhausts I
should use that
do I have to target them to do that
don't think health potions are very good
buy this guy's too good though I don't
know how to fight him
my minions are stealing the last Tetz
gods Annie I can take a knee
oh yeah skill bro
okay that guy's too good that guy's too
good um that looks pretty good
I don't know how we're gonna kill him I
kill any and that guy kills me
Oh Annie's back I can kill her perfect
love killing Annie it's a hobby
No
ah just blade and usin this ghost play
can i buy those things money
I'm not buying guardian angel again well
that one looks pretty good I wish I had
money
my team has destroyed the first time
these people are too good my book he's
killing our turret turret can you attack
him you killed our turret like I'm here
killing minions let's go kill the dragon
this guy's worse than me
Xander love killing man
oh yeah bro
no-no-no
like I don't know what I can do that guy
shows up and he's too strong and he just
kills me I don't have a choice
oh I can buy a serrated Dirk perfect
should not be buying these cheap items
what do they upgrade I don't know how
items work on this game
that guy's a new if I could kill him
okay what do I have to do keep an eye
out should I cast wards
so kill that guy
I know it's an an easy to kill Oh
die die die all right
you should sell your Dorian sword in
that hammer both my door and swords and
focus on getting which one duskblade oh
this one forgot that okay I got that now
I have to get you some as ghostblade
where is this this one okay I'll come
back when I have 2900 goals perfect you
are bro
I liked your good bro you know how to
help me out who's that guy can we kill
him oh yeah George uh-oh they're coming
for an attack oh they're here
that was a waste a nest
okay so I got a I got a get a twenty
nine hundred gold if I go jungle I don't
know what that means but I've heard
people say it on streams they say
they're gonna go jungle
well that was good while it lasted ah
I use Daffy I guess I could have tried
to use D on them hey kid double-team
okay bro I'm coming to help you out
coming to help you out
it's just not fair
going jungle is in the outskirts so that
I think we lost this game sick
oh okay they're doing okay this guy
needs to be killed but what if I show up
here he'll just kill me like it's not
fair all right let's go jungle I know I
can jungle this one so how do i market
to my allies
can I kill that
boom I juggled jungle over here
yeah we can my tower helped me there you
go
oh they just have one person who's good
minions attacking my tower sucks
don't even get any of that gold
try Junko more I feel like I didn't get
more XP from jungling that I different
just killing minions
they're in our base why don't we go
Kelvin
okay ready for the hardest fight of my
life useless
useless what's up you should be going
bottom lane but for this game just wrong
they kill him at least yell surrender
sure
you know what No Surrender
I changed my vote if I get more gold I
can buy that other thing if I just
jungle a little bit more
that was not a good use of my our
ability was it
all right let's all stick together these
minions yeah all right look at this
teamwork now
they're in our base you guys
oh these guys are noobs I can kill him
never mind they were nukes yeah use it
for the audience
they won't dead we win
33 verse 28 yeah oh I have gold now what
should I buy
I still can't afford a ghost blade I
need 500 gold
okay I need 50 more goals
my iron gold just by living this is nice
they're killing our inhibitor again now
okay but now I'm about to have a goal
and blade or whatever it is yeah I go
around blade I'm unstoppable now
okay well that lasted ten seconds
guys one of these days I'm gonna win a
league of legend name one of these days
I will win a league of legends game
one of these days no you all sucked Oh
but now I've leveled up alright let's
try it one more game let's let's keep
going
this game is addictive one day I'll be
good at it watch this vid you will laugh
only two minutes is this appropriate for
my channel my family-friendly channel
we're family-friendly here
this is long the paupers ksi
I don't know man Oh confused I'm not
much about Mike Tyson but doesn't me by
Holyfield's ear off that's all I really
know about him what if you can play
League of Legends sure you play for a
night instead I'm worse if you could
believe it I'm actually worse at 4:00 at
night than I have at League of Legends
yeah I know kid kitty pryde is lovely
Soundcloud I knew Tom Cruise a better
debt
a fortnight oh yeah except God
ah
okay so now wait wait you told me what
items I had to buy and save my money for
those items you should
so okay
focus on last enemy vengeance
and I gotta buy duskblade and ghostblade
or double blade okay
wait whatever my match
do they not find other players to match
with or as bad as me all we misfortunes
yes
you don't need to save your money so
what you need to do is click on the item
you wanna purchase and Percy item to
build the end my day thoughtful tomorrow
okay
okey one you are super bro thank you for
priming and wait um star Guardian this
oh no how does he get to be star
Guardian misfortune doesn't much sexier
looking misfortune does that cost real
money
I mean that cost real money it's almost
worth it
super for now he's super brokers he
gives me good legal legends tips unlike
you new Tom Cruise who quote my rap
lyrics he always make your aim should I
should so I should buy the door hands
blades let's see what this is what say
you moves goes played made-up long sword
and serrated Dirk okay I say duskblade
okay so maybe I shouldn't buy any door
hands blades should I not I don't even
know do I buy Dorian's blades or no
what do I save my gold and you think I
should go bot go bot
make sure you guys get Oracle ends for
chemo shrooms you got shoes bro alright
we'll go back wait but there's someone
else here kill him oh he hit me oh look
there's someone hiding there
Oh bro I think we should retreat growl
good retreat bro
putting game
all you need to do that
say go home I should go
sorry bro it wasn't good enough buy
potions ok potions are a waste of money
I'm still level one
[Applause]
oh yeah of course we get killed first
hey all the minions keep stealing the
kills
oh shit
that guy's just staying in the woods
taking potshots at you cheater
like I hate that
he's in here isn't it
when you ran away come on bitch I like
this guy's teammate though he's proud
tree for our retreat
you're going home you're going home like
bitch
nevermind your good teammate I'm sorry
no no no no no run okay I'll go home
like bitch tail
okay so now I want to buy duskblade and
ghostblade
so I buy longsword should I wait for
gold maybe I'll wait for gold is that a
good move
wait and I thought if I just have those
oh I say I understand but that okay so
that just adds a way that make sense
I'm coming ba bro get boots first okay
well I wish I knew that buy boots sorry
yeah
don't worry I shall avenge you yeah oh
is that something good
I got so much gold gnashed I go home get
boots don't get boots
shop boots of speed
Caulfield warhammer love it
I'm feeling good about this game oh they
already level seven
oh come and help you bro
want my are abilities
alright alright alright wizard guy sucks
bro bro bro bro bro bro you're
overextending bro you're gonna die
none of them running they're running
they're running you got him you got him
got him
yeah no no no yeah oh look at that use
of f Oh brawl with that skill of what
if I didn't hit that F at just the right
moment is this one good should I get
this or should I buy more of those
things I like DOS we'll buy them bro f
save me bro whoever told me about f your
bro I'll get that oh man I'm killing it
oh it's just wizard new began my now to
kill wizard noob
Oh Mykel there's no good people in this
game just wizard new and I even have my
R he won't even know what hit him
there's no shit about our
okay okay okay okay okay okay oh I don't
have to go home again
maybe I'll kill minion first cats go
home
they're taking my tower down get a
minions I don't find zero day anymore I
am legal legends and the simple player
of the League of Legends
no oh I thought I had them avenge me
brother turn around and kill wizard oh
you're new did you shot one of them down
at least
I want sexy misfortune like the other
guy had I'll pay money for it
I'll pay real money don't worry I have
real money
SiC micro brow
fuck you wizard
[Applause]
kill wizard new
I don't want the lowest-level guy in the
game now
you're going home
he's going by
yes
almost level mine
yeah I'm 18 bro oh you're cool so you
know things about League of Legends best
route to take to learn to code you just
got to do it
there's not really a route like you just
got to pick a project and you just got
to do that project right like pick
something you're interested in so you'll
stay motivated and then just work on it
and like not every part of it's gonna be
motivating but you know that's why you
got to pick something you're interested
in
do you have an F back yet oh I gotta go
home again
Nikhil our Tower two against one
don't blame me
let's go kill them how do i signal to my
enemy friends that we're gonna go Titus
but showed up yeah I love that
uh don't worry so much about language
really just work on a project but decide
what you want to exist and then work on
making it exists yeah I wish we could
have done this before they knocked our
tower down
that was great
who should we live Shu Kaggle that might
be funny no I think tag is just stupid
now
I like you can buy things
[Applause]
I moved out of my house when I was 8 no
I don't know about Kaggle like to this
merit I haven't done in a while I
remember looking at it it was just
people making these like absurd and
samba models that didn't correspond to
anything reality
I didn't like that those guys yeah
are we winning
they're all there no it's a wizard bro
where's it brother over there I'm coming
to back you up bro just hang around
I'm coming we'll go kill wizard bro
together
[Music]
this is not a good strategy no okay okay
all right I've learned something you
can't keep running when they get to the
turret
-
I was six sided to kill Oh where's the
girl you got killed by wizard bro who's
a buzz little bitch though
my wizard burgers leveled off was it
brought won't see me coming now I just
look like a minion
you push and keep pushing
what a waste of your attack
wait what how I get killed
use happen everywhere okay I didn't I
didn't agree with that decision I just
want to point that out I didn't agree
with that I know what the game did but I
didn't agree with the game's decision I
don't think it was correct I should have
died there
rush mag
you can wizard Bob I'm coming to help
you kill things
I'm getting out of there
that looks like a way to die
[Music]
yeah got him love this game
I got out of there just in time
so I turn around a fight what do I do
well you know I don't want more of those
crap
that's what I want
now I have everything you told me to buy
do it buy anything else
Oh
uh-oh this isn't sounding good wait we
have 40 is that us and we have 40 kills
they're crashing that damn viga I don't
know what a vigorous the sounds vaguely
racist music that's a little minion
fight going on here
that's cute look at little minions
fighting each other
go minions go I freaked away for you
got the turrets bro we get gold for that
no run away run away run away I don't
think I can take
come here tightest spots I need your
help
hi this butts why do you run away just
what I needed you you were my only hope
when is that okay you know what I'm just
gonna kill her
Oh
Titus butts is here love Titus but she's
bro hey what
dad dad no I'm not ordering food not
hungry
that's a ton of food tonight it's kind
of gross
how do you know what to buy anymore
this looks pretty good yeah perfect
oh we're gonna win this game I think oh
yeah we got
we got him bros we got him tightest
butts I wish you could have saved me all
right there's only a 12 I think I can
beat him let's go let's kill the dragon
love killing the dragon I'm in
I did something I'm helping
but they'll go
right away
I love dog look at that attack
oh I can recall superfast cuz I have
dragon power
C well I can run fast cuz I have dragon
power
oh this is great
look at all these minions why is all
these minions here it's gonna be so
crunchy
just one shot all those minions
oh yeah
oh I feel so nice to win a game yeah all
right Oh
Titus butts you are the number one bro
all right one more game what we're game
though gonna sleep hey Pope is go big
game yo you outside let's play my
brother's League game but we're gonna
have to play later we're gonna play
normal game now let's go
[Music]
no it's not Alex Roy it's a co-worker
oh if I teach your friends we in a bot
game in a part of bot down well I could
get any I could get perma Annie I think
I make money for streaming on Twitch I'm
not really sure how I was thinking about
writing music actually the Eminem album
is pretty inspiring always misfortune
it's just this is aspiring music
it's true
those that do a leap I don't know all
right
[Music]
sixteen-year-old bro
did I play last game better I think I've
did my loadouts better my items I gotta
buy boot stuff I know that one now
always buy boots
[Music]
you can just chat with your fans and can
make more money on touch I love making
money guys you know I love money what
life and mice you know life advice
I want League of Legends advice this one
I want I listen to you if you even if
you guys telling these stupid things on
listen hey could one of you guys Google
how to win at League of Legends and tell
me what it says
but it's damn stupid though this is
falling like
well she runs so fast but GoBot
don't Bob Bruce don't anybody else to go
back so I'm gonna buy I'm solo bye
tonight attacked our bro row let's kill
him bro so I use my health potion
already minions yep let's go home
kill him kill him kill him
yeah die oh you guys are new
why do I have a thing on my head Oh
stupid and buy things anyway
don't
uh-oh your triple box oh my god what is
this
you're gonna take down our tower
Holloway alert beep oh here
oh my god you came in and slayed them
all
you are number one okay now I liked
being solo BOTS go away oh you are great
friend you listen to me
you want to go your level shit and I'm
level awesome wait how do I get Kemp
there were two of them
cheaters oh wait I got a kilt
I
yeah
you're gonna die
no cheaters they lured me
goes play by that one I want to buy dusk
play that I don't have any more money
I wait for money yeah we can wait here
five four three two one five long so
let's go
you know diver
I'm gonna get last kill
[Music]
-
the highest level on the team oh yeah
kill
Oh
most better
I can't experience in this
that was their alternate
don't find me don't find me don't find
me don't find me don't find me don't
find me don't find me no I pressed half
it didn't help
I can't afford a duskblade of dark beer
unless I sell my boots is know by that
10 by berserker's greaves though
should I buy bass or should I wait for
that or should I buy that
damage attack speed mmm oh it's worth it
I'm alive again I gotta go
there's such low level
I will pone these noobs no we will we
will sell come by we will buy League of
Legends games
boom unstoppable
legendary
it seems like where I'm needed well it's
good here until these minions
easy
alright alright I know by that and by
that oh yeah oh now I'm unstoppable
what else should I buy
like dagger dagger sounds good
oh yeah thanks team I don't know what
that means but you're all bros love you
all
nice gross oh right that was really dumb
oops I didn't mean to do that we gotta
go we gotta go we gotta go get out of
here
so it's cool let's get that love moving
fast and breaking this guy Oh running
from them cuz they scared um such high
level I ain't scared of shit
oh he's too good
oh nice sorry I couldn't help you bros
if TR runs coding training sessions of
twitch oh yeah yeah we'll take your new
coding training after this but you all
gotta give me money pay money first
money first and then we'll do coding
trainings if you guys manage to give me
$10 before I'm done with this game of
League of Legends
we'll do some coding training after this
with the 45 minutes of Tony trainer but
only is joke
there's others that mean let's go kill
you guys give me no no no no you guys
give me money where's my money
ooh rapid firecannon love that are you
doing kills miss Jets oh we don't we're
slaying and I'm still winning I'm the
most valuable player on our team
I'm a beast so that I die I only died
cuz I play stupid overextend myself into
useless battles nice
well how fast she runs let's go miss
fortune they're all that minion gold
that could be yours
why are you guys going that way
oh that was so cheap he chained up for
us but we were killing the bird no no no
I'll do training right now but you gotta
give me ten dollars
oh the gang you're not fond of they have
high-level people and I'm the high level
person on our team and I don't know how
to play this game
we were just killing the bird and you
had to come mess with our bird
killing time by your level Tanima crush
Neal talk away from white power
that's right that hey oh hey what was
that
really am sick of the account
oh that's right but you kill them all
oh yeah gotta get him gather get up
that's right
give the last one kill the last one
golde again but what i can buy
oh and I got my special charge back up
I really am sick of dying
well be there in a minute I'll be there
in a minute
yeah this high-level
you're buying
I'll be seeing doc
see you on our team Wow I think so sweet
let's go take out their towers no no you
pay me money first and then we do
training but only tonight hey any money
$10 now and we'll do coding after this
otherwise we'll just play League of
Legends all night all right love it this
is the most popular my League of Legends
channel has ever been don't even think
about it
how are you killed yeah I woulda guessed
pyroclasm
we are all dead
oh we're all dead well they killed us
all
what can i buy
Oh self dorans blade why would I want
that
more Dominic's regards that looks cool
alright let's go kill them we are the
rightful owners of this plot of land I
you have addressed us for the last time
red team you stand for everything that
our values are not and today rock dude
69 is taking a stand for years of photo
right away is so many guys now run away
there's too many is too many with too
many run oh and you killed me up yup
that was great yeah no those dumped yeah
alright well oh well we tried I love all
of you 32 streamers you're all during my
favourite you're my favorite you're my
favorite we're gonna win this game of
League for you guys kill them kill them
please teammates go after don't know oh
yeah double kill that's right oh that's
right that's why you don't mess with
blue we killed them all but as that us
no we're good
oh yes we're back alright I'm here to
help you out let's go
all rush by for win
let's go let's go all but now
I am your leader I am Miss Fortune and I
will not guide you all
ah that was intense
okay what can I get rid of oh oh if I
get rid of health potion can I buy other
things you're curious mere
[Music]
I don't even know how to use how potions
are useless I'll look there in our base
life life life life life life life life
life life I'm gonna unleash my our
attack on them they'll never know what I
spit what came
yes that's our attack
oh well that was close that was close
yeah we best be rushed med
that's right with my mercurial schmear
oh yeah oh thank you you gave me wait
that's not $10 is that $10 all right
we'll just some we'll do some
programming after this all right let's
do some programming after we kill this
noob that's right
shit bro he got yet he got shit I don't
know how to fight him ah we're gonna
code after this freeform coding and
there might be some weed smoking after a
coating coating coating only cuz no
we've soggy for League of Legends gotta
focus when you're playing League of
Legends this is a hard game I have to
wait 30 more seconds this is bullshit I
don't even get to use my mercurial
schmear wait how come
is there no level beyond a team is that
max level that's bullshit well they
destroyed our inhibitor that's why they
get Superman
okay
well look at this little minion pile up
all right so long I've bought time die
at least I killed him oh wait we're
gonna loose we're gonna lose
we're seriously gonna lose about now the
minions are here we just lost this game
Oh No
bro you are only home Oh Mike Wow
well you are champ Wow
okay I'm gonna kill all these minions
with one super hot fire
I'm going on guys I'm going home don't
worry I'll be there soon
all right I'll told them
got'em bras all right let's go man let's
come in
whoo thousand chance
well look at that horde of minions I'm
gonna go take him out taking out that
horde guys who is never gonna see what
came
how many guys are coming
we got him
shit
this is this is close like I don't know
who wins this I've never seen a legal
legends game go on like this I don't
know what happens I'm gonna sell that I
buy that
should I get rid of my boots what is
this step
you know what happens
and I couldn't I'm not sure out of
position or daddy daddy
I share a tree
Jiji folks all those close to him
alright alright so that's $10 so we're
gonna do some program oh my god it's
late
that game was close though
yeah I'm sure one exit League legends
all right all right so we're gonna
program call it learning what do we want
- okay guys who paid for a programming
tutorial let's go do programming in PHP
we'll have PHP what have PHP mmm a dot
PHP what's a dollar sign a equals a echo
dollar sign a we're doing is syntax
highlighting for PHP don't let that PHP
a dot PHP you know I'm gonna do the PHP
for ya okay all right so notice how it
prints out the word I of course not
followed by a new line because PHP is
bad for anyone I'm gonna print this in
for the new line so we'll just Becker
slash at or that should be a new one
okay cool so now we right now you have
some PHP let's have some fun with PHP
right so we could just do like for
dollar sign a equals a dollar sign a
less than Z cosine a plus plus and then
we can like her echo a echo and write
please we'll just print out the letters
from A to Z right yeah okay so oh wait
no hang on I messed up I forgot about 0
where Z where Z oh I gotta do less than
or equal to Z right I let's go oh wait
why did it print all the way to Y Z PHP
makes no sense let's do that again in
slow motion for those of you who didn't
see okay
so very simple PHP program you can see
here I just iterate the letters a
the FNLA I print out a new line to a PHP
program okay ABCD efg hy g KY z KY okay
perfect now if I change this to a less
than or equal to we get Y Z I don't know
man PHP makes no sense okay so now that
we've all learned how to program in PHP
I hope you enjoyed you toriel a tutorial
and now it's my bedtime now I wouldn't
do that to you guys I promised you a
coding tutorial let me see if those bits
how much money art which bits worth
because guys I do love money we should
change the game we're playing though
we're playing programming I don't want
to get banned from twitch alright
perfect
how much which bits worth
this is very confusing this looks like
Amazon this looks like AWS know I hate
guardian angel never buy guardian angel
you should have seen me last night
okay guys what is no one talking
PHP game
you guys wanted me I did PHP game you
like PHP game PHP a dot PHP now what
should we Co you listen you learn okay
all right what should we code let's go
add some Python I want you be coded by
thought oh I know what I was playing
with you wanna flirt with formulas for
Gaussian poreless for gas run so now let
me know much about gaussians but we can
look at pictures of gas it's like a
Gaussian beautiful calcium's this
Gaussian is bigger than this Gaussian
but you guys know that all Gaussian
should be equal so we should multiply
that 1 by 2 because these are communist
gases let's look at them oh look at
Communist gaussians are the same right
now
yay all right now that's stupid because
now it's not a Gaussian anymore and we
have to have definition because this is
a nation of laws all right Python ah you
didn't like PHP ok fine all right um
Python object detection in 30 minutes
what object you want to detect what's
the object you'll loan that online
perfect we need Yolo net online webcam
demo Yolo life perfect
looks hard
you just want to download Yolo I mean
that's how I would do a legit detection
we can watch the Yolo video these people
know how to market check
[Music]